

tinastouch@gmail.com | (647) 282 4523 | Pickering, Ont L1V 3W9

Summary

Personable Customer Experience Manager with experience employing exceptional relationship-building abilities to cultivate positive rapport among clients, staff and management. Highly developed communicator with outstanding skills in complex problem-solving and conflict resolution. Expertise in resource allocation and schedule management.

Skills

- Websites
- Web Design
- Customer consulting
- Marketing understanding
- Staff development
- Customer Service
- Workforce Management
- Teambuilding

- Organizational skills
- Reliable and trustworthy
- Special events planning
- Schedule management
- Business Administration
- New employee training
- Inventory supplies
- Administrative operations

Experience

Service Ontario **Customer Service Representative**11/2021 - Current

- Provides comprehensive information and processing of Driver's Licenses and Health cards to a diverse base of customers
- Delivers exceptional customer service, with highly in tuned interpersonal, and communication skills
- Demonstrates analytical and problem-solving skills to probe for information, assess situations and determine appropriate course of action
- Excellent planning and organization skills to organize and prioritize workloads
- Works flexibly and collaborates well in team driven environment to ensure that operational requirements are met
- Provides General knowledge of government services and programs
- Works proficiently with word processing, spreadsheets, email and browser based applications including; CRS, RPDB, LSC and Qmatic Cloud

Island Mix Restaurant and Lounge General Manager of Operations 01/2005 - Current

- Collaborated with staff to maximize customer satisfaction, streamline procedures and improve bottom-line profitability.
- Maximized team performance by training new employees on proper food handling, guest expectations and restaurant protocols.
- Assessed operational performance to measure compliance with regulatory, industry and brand standards.
- Developed and implemented strategies to enhance team performance, improve processes and increase efficiency.
- Scheduled and directed staff in daily work assignments to maximize productivity.

- Counseled and disciplined staff, addressing issues promptly and providing constructive feedback.
- Efficiently resolved problems or concerns to satisfaction of all involved parties.
- Tina's Touch Established

 Versatile Artist Sole Proprietorship

 11/2007 Current
- Design Business cards, Flyers, Logos, Tattoos, Wedding stationary, Websites.
- Fine Artist Acrylic paintings, Drawings, Manufacturing Woodwork and Plastics.
- Photography Events, Portraits, Weddings, Creative Photo shoots, Maternity.
- Event Planner Décor, Coordination, planning.
- Interfaced with clients and customers to determine special art project needs, prepared design proposals, and defined project scope.
- Drove business growth and community visibility through implementation of targeted marketing and sales strategies.

Home Depot Paint Sales Associate 2010 - 2012

- Assisted customers with the correct selection and purchase of Paint colors & Paint Types
- Mix Paint using a computerized paint dispenser
- Received training in all paints and stains
- Provided a high degree of customer service to drive customer satisfaction

Education and Training

Shaw Academy Illustrator Diploma Photoshop Diploma Photography Diploma Graphic Design Diploma 2020/2021

Ontario College of Art and Design **Web Design** 2013

Digital Publishing Certificate part time student 2011

Ontario College of Art and Design Bachelor Degree of Fine Arts 2007

References Available Upon Request